awardsplatform.com 2019-06-02

# Privacy Policy — Awards Management Software

Effective date: 20 May, 2018

Award Force Pty Ltd ("us", "we", or "our") operates the Award Force cloud software and the Award Force website [www.awardforce.com](https://www.awardforce.com/) (the "Service").

Award Force is committed to providing you with the best possible experience, which includes the security, privacy and integrity of your personal data. Award Force complies with the requirements of:

  * The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) as set out in the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council, of 27 April 2016
  * The Australian Privacy Principles as set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from [www.awardforce.com/agreement](https://www.awardforce.com/agreement)

## Definitions

### Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

### Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

You can read more about the cookies we use on our website here.

### Data Controller

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

### Data Processor (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

### Data Subject

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

### User

The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

## Information collection and use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Types of data collected

 **Personal Data**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Phone number
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
  * Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

 **Usage Data**

We may also collect information on how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's IP address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

 **Tracking Cookies Data**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyse our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  *  **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  *  **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  *  **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

View our Cookies Policy page which which provides further detail on what information we gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies.

## Use of data

Award Force Pty Ltd uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

## Retention of data

Award Force Pty Ltd will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Award Force Pty Ltd will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

## Transfer of data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to— and maintained on— computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside the European Union (EU) and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the EU and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Award Force Pty Ltd will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure of data

### Business transaction

If Award Force Pty Ltd is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

### Legal requirements

Award Force Pty Ltd may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Award Force Pty Ltd
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

## Security of data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable, best practice, and state-of-the-art means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## "Do Not Track" signals

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

## Your rights

Award Force Pty Ltd aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you
  * To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
  * To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to Award Force Pty Ltd. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

## Service providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analysing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyse the use of our Service.

 **Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalise the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

**ClientSuccess**

For users of our product, we provide a limited amount of your information to ClientSuccess, Inc. and utilise ClientSuccess to collect performance data for analytics and business process purposes. ClientSuccess may make use of cookies, to track our relationship so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on the privacy practices of ClientSuccess, please visit their privacy policy at [https://www.clientsuccess.com/privacy-policy/ ](https://www.clientsuccess.com/privacy-policy/)

**Intercom**

We provide a limited amount of your information (such as sign-up date and some personal information like your email address) to Intercom, Inc. (“Intercom”) and utilize Intercom to collect data for analytics purposes when you visit our website or use our product. As a data processor acting on our behalf, Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or product and tracks our relationship by way of cookies and similar technologies so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on Intercom's use of cookies, please visit <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#cookie-policy>. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s). As part of our service agreements, Intercom collects publicly available contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender, company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses, to enhance your user experience. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy>. Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use which can be found at <https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms>. If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please contact us.

 **Mouseflow**

This website uses Mouseflow: a website analytics tool that provides session replay, heatmaps, funnels, form analytics, feedback campaigns, and similar features/functionality. Mouseflow may record your clicks, mouse movements, scrolling, form fills (keystrokes) in non-excluded fields, pages visited and content, time on site, browser, operating system, device type (desktop/tablet/phone), screen resolution, visitor type (first time/returning), referrer, anonymized IP address, location (city/country), language, and similar metadata. Mouseflow does not collect any information on pages where it is not installed, nor does it track or collect information outside your web browser. If you'd like to opt-out, you can do so at https://mouseflow.com/opt-out. If you'd like to obtain a copy of your data, make a correction, or have it erased, please contact us first or, as a secondary option, contact Mouseflow at privacy@mouseflow.com. For more information, see Mouseflow’s Privacy Policy at <http://mouseflow.com/privacy/>. For more information on Mouseflow and GDPR, visit <https://mouseflow.com/gdpr/>.

 **New Relic**

For users of our product, we use New Relic, a performance monitoring and analytics service. New Relic may make use of cookies, to track our relationship so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on the privacy practices of New Relic, please visit their privacy policy at <https://newrelic.com/termsandconditions/privacy>

**Pusher**

For users of our product, we use Pusher, a push notification service. Pusher may make use of cookies, to track product interactions and facilitate notifications to you. For more information on the privacy practices of Pusher, please visit their privacy policy at [https://pusher.com/legal/privacy ](https://pusher.com/legal/privacy)

### Behavioural remarketing

Award Force Pty Ltd uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimise and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

 **Google AdWords**

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> \- for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

**LinkedIn**

LinkedIn retargeting service is provided by LinkedIn Ireland U.C.

You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of LinkedIn by visiting their Privacy Policy page: <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy>

 **Twitter**

Twitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc.

You can opt-out from Twitter's interest-based ads by following their instructions: <https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405>

You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by visiting their Privacy Policy page: <https://twitter.com/privacy>

**Facebook**

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>

To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada <http://youradchoices.ca/> or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy: <https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>

### Marketing

Award Force Pty Ltd uses third party marketing services to support our marketing activities. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to continuously improve the marketing of our Service.

 **AutoPilot**

For users of our website, we provide a limited amount of your information to AutoPilot, an automated marketing service. Data entered into forms on our website is processed by AutoPilot. AutoPilot may make use of cookies, to track our relationship so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on the privacy practices of AutoPilot, please visit their privacy policy at <https://autopilothq.com/privacypolicy.html>

**Capterra**

For users of our website, we use Capterra, a software review service. Capterra may make use of cookies, to track our relationship so that we can improve our marketing. For more information on the privacy practices of Capterra, please visit their privacy policy at <https://www.capterra.com/legal/privacy-policy>

**G2 Crowd**

For users of our website, we use Capterra, a software review service. Capterra may make use of cookies, to track our relationship so that we can improve our marketing. For more information on the privacy practices of Capterra, please visit their privacy policy at <https://www.g2crowd.com/static/privacy>

**Squarespace**

For users of our website, we provide a limited amount of your information to Squarespace, a website building tool. Data entered into forms on our website is processed by Squarespace. Squarespace may make use of cookies, to track our relationship so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on the privacy practices of Squarespace, please visit their privacy policy at <https://www.squarespace.com/privacy>

### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

 **Authorize.Net**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/>

**BluePay**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.bluepay.com/privacy-policy/>

**BPOINT (Commonwealth Bank)**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.commbank.com.au/security-privacy/general-security/privacy.html>

**CyberSource**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.cybersource.com/privacy/>

**eWay**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.eway.com.au/legal#privacy>

**NAB Transact**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.nab.com.au/common/privacy-policy>

**Netbanx (Paysafe)**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.paysafe.com/legal-and-compliance/privacy-policy/>

**PayPal**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>

**Realex Payments**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.globalpaymentsinc.com/en-ie/accept-payments/ecommerce/privacy>

**Sage Pay**  
Their policies can be viewed at <https://www.sagepay.co.uk/policies>

**SecurePay**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.securepay.com.au/privacy-policy/>

**Stripe**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>

**Westpac PayWay**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://www.westpac.com.au/privacy/full-privacy-policy/>

**WorldPay**  
Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.worldpay.com/uk/privacy-policy ](https://www.worldpay.com/uk/privacy-policy)

## Links to other sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children's privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children" or "Child").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from Children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes to this privacy policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact us

If you have any questions or requests in relation to this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@awardforce.com](mailto:privacy@awardforce.com)
